Guide to the Meyer Chessin Papers 1930-1992
Maureen and Mike Mansfield Library, The University of Montana--Missoula
- Civic and Environmental Service Papers, 1959-1982; Series VI; 4.4 linear feet
  - Nuclear Weapons’ effects, Bikini clippings, 1977 (Box-folder 19/34)
  - Nuclear Weapons and Radiation effects, 1960-1978 and undated (Box-folder 19/35)
  - Nuclear Weapons and Radiation, 1962-1977 and undated (Box-folder 19/36)
  - Nuclear Winter, articles, undated (Box-folder 19/37)
  - Oregon Bottle Bill, 1973 and undated (Box-folder 19/38)
  - Overkill/Overrun movie, correspondence and flyers, 1972 (Box-folder 19/39)
  - Peace, articles and correspondence, 1960-1968 (Box-folder 19/40)
  - Pesticides, undated (Box-folder 19/41)
  - Pesticides, undated (Box-folder 20/1)
  - Petitions, undated (Box-folder 20/2)
  - Public Concerns, correspondence, articles, and clippings, 1970-1980 (Box-folder 20/3)
  - Radiation, undated (Box-folder 20/4)
  - Radiation, clippings, 1970-1977 and undated (Box-folder 20/5)
  - Radiation, correspondence, 1962-1972 (Box-folder 20/6)
  - Radiation and air pollution research, undated (Box-folder 20/7)
  - Radiation Biology, local outline and notes, undated (Box-folder 20/8)
  - Radiation Biology, correspondence, undated (Box-folder 20/9)
  - Radiation Fallout and Pollution, undated (Box-folder 20/10-12)
  - Radioactivity, biological effects, 1966-1975 (Box-folder 20/13)
  - Radiology, undated (Box-folder 20/14)
  - Recycling, undated (Box-folder 20/15)
  - Recycling program in Rochester, New York, undated (Box-folder 20/16)
  - Rocky Mountain Science Council, newsletter, 1965 (Box-folder 20/17)
  - Sagebrush, undated (Box-folder 20/18)
  - Sagebrush, correspondence, undated (Box-folder 20/19)
  - Sagebrush and other mass sprayings in Montana, undated (Box-folder 20/19)
  - Sagebrush, paper, undated (Box-folder 20/20)
  - Sagebrush, research, undated (Box-folder 20/21)
  - Science and public policy, undated (Box-folder 20/22)
  - Scientists Institute for Public Information, undated (Box-folder 20/23)
  - Social Action Committee for Communications, undated (Box-folder 20/24)
  - Solid Waste education, undated (Box-folder 20/25)
  - Solid Waste education, undated (Box-folder 20/26)
  - Solid Waste management, undated (Box-folder 20/27)
  - Solid Waste Workshop, undated (Box-folder 20/28-30)
  - Solid Waste Workshop, 1973 (Box-folder 20/31)
  - Solid Waste Workshop, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 20/32)
  - Solid Waste Workshop, Billings, Montana, undated (Box-folder 20/33)
  - Solid Waste Workshop, Billings, Montana, undated (Box-folder 21/1)
  - Solid Waste Workshop, correspondence, undated (Box-folder 21/2-3)
  - Solid Waste Workshop, educational materials, undated (Box-folder 21/4)
  - Solid Waste Workshop, financial records, undated (Box-folder 21/5)
  - Solid Waste Workshop, final summary, circa 1970s (Box-folder 21/6)
  - Solid Waste Workshop, grant application, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 21/7)
  - Solid Waste Workshop, Great Falls, Montana, undated (Box-folder 21/8)
  - Solid Waste Workshop, Helena, Montana, 1973 (Box-folder 21/9-10)
  - Solid Waste Workshop, materials, undated (Box-folder 21/11)
  - Solid Waste Workshop, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box-folder 21/12)
  - Solid Waste Workshop, newsletter, undated (Box-folder 21/13)
  - Solid Waste Workshop, notes, undated (Box-folder 21/14)
  - Solid Waste Workshop, Pocatello, Idaho, undated (Box-folder 21/15-16)
  - Solid Waste Workshop, Pocatello, Idaho, summary and analysis, 1974 (Box-folder 21/17)
  - Solid Waste Workshop, programs, undated (Box-folder 21/18)
  - Solid Waste Workshop, publicity, undated (Box-folder 21/19)
  - Solid Waste Workshop, recycling information, undated (Box-folder 21/20)
  - Solid Waste Workshop, Spokane, Washington, undated (Box-folder 21/21-24)
  - Solid Waste Workshop, weekly meeting notes, undated (Box-folder 21/25)
  - Soviet Energy, undated (Box-folder 21/26)
  - Survival?, undated (Box-folder 21/27)
  - Teach-in, correspondence and petition, undated (Box-folder 21/28)
  - Test Ban Treaty, correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 21/29)
  - Test Ban Treaty, Amchitka, undated (Box-folder 21/30)
  - Test Ban Treaty, congressional records, undated (Box-folder 21/31)
  - Test Ban Treaty, Montana, Canada and Nevada, undated (Box-folder 21/32)
  - Test Ban Treaty, radiation, undated (Box-folder 21/33)
  - Test Ban Treaty, radiation, Hosmer, undated (Box-folder 21/34)
  - US Military Resources, correspondence, 1976 (Box-folder 22/1)
  - Vietnam, undated (Box-folder 22/2)
  - Vietnam, correspondence, clippings and articles, 1964-1972 (Box-folder 22/3-4)
  - Weed Control, regional, undated (Box-folder 22/5)
  - Western Montana Scientists Committee for Public Information (WMSCPI), undated (Box-folder 22/6-8)
  - WMSCPI, conference and meeting minutes, 1972-1982 (Box-folder 22/9)
  - WMSCPI, contact information, undated (Box-folder 22/10)
- College Papers, 1940-1948; Series VII; 1.0 linear foot
  - College Papers, 1946-1948 (Box-folder 23)
  - College Papers, 1946-1948 (Box-folder 24)
  - College Papers, 1940-1943 (Box-folder 25)
- Miscellaneous Papers, 1974; Series VIII; 0.4 linear feet
  - Business cards, undated (Box-folder 26/1)
  - Calendar, 1974 (Box-folder 26/2)
  - Clippings, undated (Box-folder 26/3)
  - Letterheads and envelopes, undated (Box-folder 26/4-6)
  - Map and notes, undated (Box-folder 26/7)
  - Notebooks, undated (Box-folder 26/8)
  - Notes, undated (Box-folder 26/9-13)
  - Notes from unidentified speech, undated (Box-folder 26/14)
  - Suppliers, undated (Box-folder 26/15)
  - University history, undated (Box-folder 26/16)
- Photographs and Slides, 1971-1975; Series IX; 1.0 linear foot
  - Cactus virus, undated (Box-folder 27)
  - Israel, 1975 (Box-folder 27)
  - King Cole's Hole, 1974 (Box-folder 27)
  - Herbicides, animal effects, 1971 (Box-folder 27)
  - Plant species from unidentified botanical gardens, undated (Box-folder 27)
  - Unidentified Photographs, undated (Box-folder 27)